Henry A. Kissinger Papers, Part III: Guide to the Yale University Library Collection
Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1941 - 2009; Series I
  - New York office
    - 2003
      - Bor-Boy, 2003 (Box 66, Folder 9)
      - Bra-Bri, 2002 - 2003 (Box 66, Folder 10)
      - Broa-Broo, 2002 - 2003 (Box 67, Folder 1)
      - Brow-Brun, 2003 - 2004 (Box 67, Folder 2)
      - Buc-Bus, 2002 - 2003 (Box 67, Folder 3)
      - But, 2003 (Box 67, Folder 4)
      - Blackwill, Robert D., 2003 (Box 67, Folder 5)
      - Bush, George W., 2003 January-April (Box 67, Folder 6)
      - Bush, George W., 2003 May-November (Box 67, Folder 7)
      - Cab-Cap, 2003 (Box 67, Folder 8)
      - Cara-Carn, 2003 (Box 67, Folder 9)
      - Carr, 2003 (Box 67, Folder 10)
      - Cart-Cast, 2003 (Box 68, Folder 1)
      - Cat-Cbs, 2003 (Box 68, Folder 2)
      - Ce, 2003 - 2004 (Box 68, Folder 3)
      - Cha-Che, 2003 (Box 68, Folder 4)
      - Chic-Chil, 2003 (Box 68, Folder 5)
      - China C-I, 2003 (Box 68, Folder 6)
      - China M-China's, 2003 (Box 68, Folder 7)
      - Chip-Chur, 2003 (Box 68, Folder 8)
      - Ci-Cn, 2002 - 2003 (Box 68, Folder 9)
      - Coa-Col, 2002 - 2003 (Box 68, Folder 10)
      - Com-Cop, 2002 - 2003 (Box 69, Folder 1)
      - Cor-Cox, 2003 (Box 69, Folder 2)
      - Cr-Ct, 2003 (Box 69, Folder 3)
      - Cu-Cz, 2003 (Box 69, Folder 4)
      - China, 2003 February-September (Box 69, Folder 5)
      - China, 2003 October-December (Box 69, Folder 6)
      - Council of the Americas, 2003 (Box 69, Folder 7)
      - Dai-Dar, 2002 - 2003 (Box 69, Folder 8)
      - Das-Day, 2003 (Box 69, Folder 9)
      - Dea, 2003 (Box 69, Folder 10)
      - Deb-Deo, 2003 (Box 70, Folder 1)
      - Dep, 2002 - 2003 (Box 70, Folder 2)
      - Der-Dic, 2003 (Box 70, Folder 3)
      - Die-Dil, 2003 (Box 70, Folder 4)
      - Dim-Dje, 2003 (Box 70, Folder 5)
      - Dn-Do, 2002 - 2003 (Box 70, Folder 6)
      - Dr, 2002 - 2003 (Box 70, Folder 7)
      - Du-Dy, 2003 - 2004 (Box 70, Folder 8)
      - Ea-Ed, 2003 (Box 70, Folder 9)
      - Eg-En, 2002 - 2003 (Box 70, Folder 10)
      - Er-Ex, 2003 (Box 71, Folder 1)
      - Epstein, Ed, 2003 (Box 71, Folder 2)
      - Fa-Fe, 1973 - 1975; 2000 - 2003 (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - Fia-Fin, 1987; 2002 - 2003 (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - Fio-Flo [includes photographs], 2002 - 2003 (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - Foer-Fore, 1957 - 1963; 1995 - 2003 (Box 71, Folder 6)
      - Fors-Foxm, 2003 (Box 71, Folder 7)
      - Fra-Fre, 2002 - 2003 (Box 71, Folder 8)
      - Fri-Fus, 2003 (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - Foreign Policy Research Institute, 2002 December-2003 July (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - Foreign Policy Research Institute, 2003 August-December (Box 72, Folder 3)
      - Ga, 2003 (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - Gee-Geo, 2002 - 2003 (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - Ger-Gil, 2002 - 2004 (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - Gin-Gno, 2003 (Box 72, Folder 7)
      - Go, 2002 - 2003 (Box 72, Folder 8)
      - Grah-Gran, 1992 - 2003 (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - Grau, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 2)
      - Grea-Gree, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - Greg-Gyll, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 4)
      - Ginsburg, David, 2002 - 2003 (Box 73, Folder 5)
      - Grant, William, 1992 - 2003 (Box 73, Folder 6)
      - Haa-Hag, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 7)
      - Hai-Han, 2002 - 2003 (Box 73, Folder 8)
      - Hana-Hang, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 9)
      - Hanh-Hans, 2002 - 2003 (Box 74, Folder 1)
      - Hara-Hart, 2003 - 2004 (Box 74, Folder 2)
      - Harv-Hayn, 2003 (Box 74, Folder 3)
      - Hbo-Heb, 2003 (Box 74, Folder 4)
      - Hef-Hew, 2003 (Box 74, Folder 5)
      - Hi, 2003 (Box 74, Folder 6)
      - Hoa-Hol [includes photographs], 2003 - 2004 (Box 74, Folder 7)
      - Hoo-Hou [includes photograph], 2002 - 2003 (Box 74, Folder 8)
      - Hov-Htm, 2002 - 2003 (Box 74, Folder 9)
      - Hua-Hus, 2002 - 2003 (Box 75, Folder 1)
      - Hut-Hym, 2003 (Box 75, Folder 2)
      - Hebrew Home for the Aged, 2002 - 2003 (Box 75, Folder 3)
      - Ily-Int, 2002 - 2003 (Box 75, Folder 4)
      - International A-F, 2003 (Box 75, Folder 5)
      - International H-S, 2003 (Box 75, Folder 6)
      - International V-W, 2003 (Box 75, Folder 7)
      - Ip-Ir, 2003 (Box 75, Folder 8)
      - Isa-Isl, 2003 (Box 75, Folder 9)
      - Isr, 2003 - 2004 (Box 75, Folder 10)
      - It-Iv, 2003 - 2004 (Box 75, Folder 11)
      - India [1 of 2], 2002 - 2003 (Box 76, Folder 1)
      - India [2 of 2], 2002 - 2003 (Box 76, Folder 2)
      - International Crisis Group (ICG), 2003 June 11-July 16 (Box 76, Folder 3)
      - International Crisis Group (ICG), 2003 July 17-July 30 (Box 76, Folder 4)
      - International Crisis Group (ICG), 2003 November (Box 76, Folder 5)
      - International Crisis Group (ICG), 2003 December (Box 76, Folder 6)
      - Investigative Project, 2003 (Box 76, Folder 7)
      - Jac, 2003 (Box 76, Folder 8)
      - Jah-Jap, 2002 - 2003 (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - Jc-Ji, 2003 (Box 77, Folder 2)
      - Joc-Jon, 1999 - 2003 (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - Jor-Jun, 2001 - 2004 (Box 77, Folder 4)
      - Kag-Kan, 2003 (Box 77, Folder 5)
      - Kap-Kat, 2002 - 2003 (Box 77, Folder 6)
      - Kau-Kek, 2002 - 2003 (Box 77, Folder 7)
      - Kel-Kha, 2003 (Box 77, Folder 8)
      - Kic-Kir, 2002 - 2003 (Box 77, Folder 9)
      - Kis-Kno, 1962; 2002 - 2005 (Box 78, Folder 1)
      - Kob-Koc, 2003 (Box 78, Folder 2)
      - Koch, 2002 - 2003 (Box 78, Folder 3)
      - Koh-Kop, 2003 (Box 78, Folder 4)
      - Kore, 2002 - 2003 (Box 78, Folder 5)
      - Korn-Kozo, 2002 - 2003 (Box 78, Folder 6)
      - Kr-Kt, 2003 (Box 78, Folder 7)
      - Ku-Kx, 2003 (Box 78, Folder 8)
      - Korda, Margaret and Michael, 2003 (Box 78, Folder 9)
      - Lac-Lap, 2003 (Box 78, Folder 10)
      - Lar-Lbc, 2002 - 2003 (Box 79, Folder 1)
      - Lea-Lel, 2003 (Box 79, Folder 2)
      - Lem-Leo, 2003 (Box 79, Folder 3)
      - Lep-Lex, 2003 (Box 79, Folder 4)
      - Li-Lj, 2003 (Box 79, Folder 5)
      - Loc-Lon [includes photograph], 2002 - 2003 (Box 79, Folder 6)
      - Lor-Lyd, 1986; 2003 (Box 79, Folder 7)
      - Mac-Mal, 2003 (Box 79, Folder 8)
      - Man, 2003 (Box 79, Folder 9)
      - Mar-Mas, 2003 (Box 79, Folder 10)
      - Mat-Mau, 2003 (Box 80, Folder 1)
      - Maw-May, 2003 (Box 80, Folder 2)
      - Mca-Mcg, 2002 - 2003 (Box 80, Folder 3)
      - Mcl-Mcw, 2003 (Box 80, Folder 4)
      - Mea-Met, 2002 - 2003 (Box 80, Folder 5)
      - Mex, 2003 (Box 80, Folder 6)
      - Mey-Mhz, 2003 (Box 80, Folder 7)
      - Mi [includes photograph], 1976; 2003 (Box 80, Folder 8)
      - Mod-Mon, 2003 (Box 80, Folder 9)
      - Mor-Mun [includes photographs], 2002 - 2003 (Box 80, Folder 10)
      - Mur, 2003 (Box 81, Folder 1)
      - Mus-Mut, 2002 - 2003 (Box 81, Folder 2)
      - My, 2002 - 2003 (Box 81, Folder 3)
      - Na-Nd, 2001 - 2003 (Box 81, Folder 4)
      - National A-P, 2002 - 2003 (Box 81, Folder 5)
      - National R-U, 2003 (Box 81, Folder 6)
      - Nec-New M, 2002 - 2003 (Box 81, Folder 7)
      - New York A-O, 2003 (Box 81, Folder 8)
      - New York P, 2003 (Box 81, Folder 9)
      - New York R-U, 2003 (Box 81, Folder 10)
      - New Yorke-Nic, 2003 - 2004 (Box 81, Folder 11)
      - Nie-Ntw, 2002 - 2003 (Box 81, Folder 12)
      - Nu-Nz, 2003 - 2004 (Box 81, Folder 13)
      - Oa-Ol, 2002 - 2003 (Box 81, Folder 14)
      - Or-Ow, 2000 - 2003 (Box 82, Folder 1)
      - Pac-Pal, 2003 (Box 82, Folder 2)
      - Pan, 2003 (Box 82, Folder 3)
      - Par-Pav, 2003 (Box 82, Folder 4)
      - Pea-Pep, 2003 (Box 82, Folder 5)
      - Per, 2002 - 2003 (Box 82, Folder 6)
      - Pet-Pew, 2003 (Box 82, Folder 7)
      - Pfl-Pil [includes photographs], 2001 - 2003 (Box 82, Folder 8)
      - Pin-Pop, 2003 (Box 82, Folder 9)
      - Por-Pra, 2003 (Box 82, Folder 10)
      - Pre-Pro, 2003 (Box 82, Folder 11)
      - Pu, 2002 - 2003 (Box 83, Folder 1)
      - Powell, Colin, 2003 (Box 83, Folder 2)
      - Project for the New American Century (PNAC), 2003 (Box 83, Folder 3)
      - Q, 2003 (Box 83, Folder 4)
      - Rab-Rap, 2003 (Box 83, Folder 5)
      - Ras-Ren, 2003 (Box 83, Folder 6)
      - Rep-Rho, 2003 (Box 83, Folder 7)
      - Ri, 2002 - 2003 (Box 83, Folder 8)
      - Rn, 2003 (Box 83, Folder 9)
      - Roa-Roc, 2002 - 2003 (Box 83, Folder 10)
      - Rod-Ron, 2003 (Box 83, Folder 11)
      - Roo-Rot, 2001 - 2003 (Box 83, Folder 12)
      - Rov-Ruh, 2003 (Box 83, Folder 13)
      - Rum-Rus, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 1)
      - Rut-Ryu, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 2)
      - Rice, Condoleezza, 2003 January-March (Box 84, Folder 3)
      - Rice, Condoleezza, 2003 April-November (Box 84, Folder 4)
      - Rumsfeld, Donald, 2002 - 2003 (Box 84, Folder 5)
      - Sab-Sai, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 6)
      - Sal-Saw, 2002 - 2003 (Box 84, Folder 7)
      - Scai-Schl, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 8)
      - Schm-Schn, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 9)
      - Scho-Schr, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 10)
      - Schu, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 11)
      - Schw, 2002 - 2003 (Box 84, Folder 12)
      - Sci-Sen, 2003 (Box 85, Folder 1)
      - Seo-Sey, 2002 - 2004 (Box 85, Folder 2)
      - Sgi-She, 2003 (Box 85, Folder 3)
      - Shi-Shu, 2003 (Box 85, Folder 4)
      - Sib-Sil, 2003 (Box 85, Folder 5)
      - Sim, 2002 - 2003 (Box 85, Folder 6)
      - Sin-Sip, 2003 (Box 85, Folder 7)
      - Sis-Sly, 2002 - 2003 (Box 85, Folder 8)
      - Sm, 2003 (Box 85, Folder 9)
      - So, 2002 - 2003 (Box 85, Folder 10)
      - Spa, 2003 (Box 85, Folder 11)
      - Spe, 2003 - 2004 (Box 86, Folder 1)
      - Spi-Srd, 2003 (Box 86, Folder 2)
      - Sta-Ste, 2003 - 2004 (Box 86, Folder 3)
      - Sto-Str, 2002 - 2003 (Box 86, Folder 4)
      - Su-Sw, 2003 (Box 86, Folder 5)
      - Sy, 2003 (Box 86, Folder 6)
      - Schmidt, Helmut, 2003 (Box 86, Folder 7)
      - Schouten, Schuyler, 2003 (Box 86, Folder 8)
      - Simon & Schuster, 2003 (Box 86, Folder 9)
      - V, 2003 (Box 86, Folder 10)
      - W, 2003 (Box 86, Folder 11)
      - Y, 2003 (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - 2004
      - Aa-Ab, 2004 (Box 86, Folder 13)
      - Ad, 2004 (Box 86, Folder 14)
      - Af-Ag, 2004 (Box 87, Folder 1)
      - Ai-Al, 2004 (Box 87, Folder 2)
      - Ama-Amb, 2004 (Box 87, Folder 3)
      - America C-American A, 2004 (Box 87, Folder 4)
      - American B-M, 2004 (Box 87, Folder 5)
      - American P-Americas, 2004 (Box 87, Folder 6)
      - An, 2004 (Box 87, Folder 7)
      - Ap, 2004 (Box 87, Folder 8)
      - Ar, 2004 (Box 87, Folder 9)
      - As, 2004 (Box 87, Folder 10)
      - At-Az, 2003 - 2004 (Box 87, Folder 11)
      - Aaron, David L., 2004 (Box 88, Folder 1)
      - American Enterprise Institute (AEI), 2004 January-March (Box 88, Folder 2)
      - American Enterprise Institute (AEI), 2004 April-May (Box 88, Folder 3)
      - American Enterprise Institute (AEI), 2004 June-December (Box 88, Folder 4)
      - Attali, Jacques, 2003 - 2004 (Box 88, Folder 5)
      - Bab-Bar, 2004 (Box 88, Folder 6)
      - Bas-Bat, 2004 (Box 88, Folder 7)
      - Bbc-Ber, 2004 (Box 88, Folder 8)
      - Bes-Bla, 2004 - 2005 (Box 88, Folder 9)
      - Ble-Bna, 2004 (Box 88, Folder 10)
      - Bo-Bp, 2004 (Box 89, Folder 1)
      - Bra-Bri, 2004 (Box 89, Folder 2)
      - Bro-Brz, 2004 (Box 89, Folder 3)
      - Buc-Bun, 2004 (Box 89, Folder 4)
      - Bus, 2003 - 2004 (Box 89, Folder 5)
      - Blumenthal, W. Michael [1 of 2], 2003 - 2004 (Box 89, Folder 6)
      - Blumenthal, W. Michael [2 of 2], 2003 - 2004 (Box 89, Folder 7)
      - Bush-Cheney '04, 2004 (Box 89, Folder 8)
      - Cab-Cap, 2004 (Box 89, Folder 9)
      - Card-Carr [includes photograph], 2004 (Box 89, Folder 10)
      - Cars-Cavu, 2004 (Box 90, Folder 1)
      - Cb-Ce, 2003 - 2004 (Box 90, Folder 2)
      - Cha-Che, 2004 (Box 90, Folder 3)
      - Chi, 2004 (Box 90, Folder 4)
      - Chr-Civ, 2003 - 2004 (Box 90, Folder 5)
      - Cl-Co, 2004 (Box 90, Folder 6)
      - Coe-Com, 2004 (Box 90, Folder 7)
      - Con-Cos, 2004 (Box 90, Folder 8)
      - Cou, 2004 (Box 90, Folder 9)
      - Cr, 2004 - 2005 (Box 90, Folder 10)
      - Cu-Cz, 2004 (Box 90, Folder 11)
      - China, 2004 January-June (Box 90, Folder 12)
      - China, 2004 July (Box 91, Folder 1)
      - China, 2004 September-December (Box 91, Folder 2)
      - Courtis, Kenneth S., 2003 - 2004 (Box 91, Folder 3)
      - Daa-Dav, 2004 (Box 91, Folder 4)
      - Day, 2004 (Box 91, Folder 5)
      - De, 2004 (Box 91, Folder 6)
      - Di, 2003 - 2004 (Box 91, Folder 7)
      - Do, 2004 (Box 91, Folder 8)
      - Dr-Du, 2003 - 2005 (Box 91, Folder 9)
      - Dilenschneider, Jan and Robert L., 2004 (Box 91, Folder 10)
      - Ea-En, 2004 - 2005 (Box 92, Folder 1)
      - Ep-Er, 2003 - 2004 (Box 92, Folder 2)
      - Es-Ex, 2004 (Box 92, Folder 3)
      - Fa-Fe, 2003 - 2004 (Box 92, Folder 4)
      - Fid-Fin, 2003 - 2004 (Box 92, Folder 5)
      - Fio-Fit, 2004 (Box 92, Folder 6)
      - Fj-Fl, 2003 - 2004 (Box 92, Folder 7)
      - Foco-Ford, 2004 (Box 92, Folder 8)
      - Fore-Fort, 2004 (Box 92, Folder 9)
      - Fou-Fox, 2004 (Box 93, Folder 1)
      - Fr-Fu, 2003 - 2004 (Box 93, Folder 2)
      - Foreign Policy Research Institute, 2004 January-May (Box 93, Folder 3)
      - Foreign Policy Research Institute, 2004 June-October (Box 93, Folder 4)
      - Foreign Policy Research Institute, 2004 November-December (Box 93, Folder 5)
      - Ga, 2004 (Box 93, Folder 6)
      - Ge, 2004 (Box 93, Folder 7)
      - Gh, 2004 (Box 94, Folder 1)
      - Gi-Gn, 2004 (Box 94, Folder 2)
      - Gol, 2003 - 2004 (Box 94, Folder 3)
      - Goo-Gov, 2004 (Box 94, Folder 4)
      - Gq, 2004 (Box 94, Folder 5)
      - Gra, 2004 (Box 94, Folder 6)
      - Gre-Gru, 2004 (Box 94, Folder 7)
      - Gu, 2004 (Box 94, Folder 8)
      - Graubard, Stephen, 2004 January-April (Box 94, Folder 9)
      - Graubard, Stephen, 2004 July-December (Box 94, Folder 10)
      - Haa-Ham, 2004 (Box 95, Folder 1)
      - Han [includes photographs], 2004 (Box 95, Folder 2)
      - Har, 2004 (Box 95, Folder 3)
      - Has-Hbo, 2003 - 2004 (Box 95, Folder 4)
      - Hea-Hen, 2004 (Box 95, Folder 5)
      - Her, 2004 (Box 95, Folder 6)
      - Hi, 2004 (Box 95, Folder 7)
      - Hof-Hoo, 2003 - 2004 (Box 95, Folder 8)
      - Hor-Hym, 2004 (Box 95, Folder 9)
      - Hoffmann, Hubertus, 2004 (Box 153, Folder 1)
      - Ide-Inm, 2004 (Box 96, Folder 1)
      - Int, 2004 (Box 96, Folder 2)
      - Ir-Iw, 2004 (Box 96, Folder 3)
      - International Crisis Group (ICG), 2004 February-June (Box 96, Folder 4)
      - International Crisis Group (ICG), 2004 July-October (Box 96, Folder 5)
      - Investigative Project, 2004 (Box 96, Folder 6)
      - Iraq material from Carol Basir, 2004 (Box 96, Folder 7)
      - Jac-Jan, 2004 (Box 96, Folder 8)
      - Jap-Jaz, 2004 (Box 96, Folder 9)
      - Jd-Jj, 2003 - 2004 (Box 97, Folder 1)
      - Joc-Joh, 2004 (Box 97, Folder 2)
      - Jon-Jun, 2003 - 2006 (Box 97, Folder 3)
      - Jacobs, Eli, 2004 (Box 97, Folder 4)
      - Kab-Kau, 2004 (Box 97, Folder 5)
      - Kaz, 2004 (Box 97, Folder 6)
      - Kea-Kes, 2004 (Box 97, Folder 7)
      - Key, 2004 (Box 97, Folder 8)
      - Kic-Kim, 2003 - 2004 (Box 97, Folder 9)
      - Kin-Kli, 2002 - 2004 (Box 97, Folder 10)
      - Koc-Koh, 2003 - 2004 (Box 98, Folder 1)
      - Kol-Kop, 2004 (Box 98, Folder 2)
      - Kor, 2004 (Box 98, Folder 3)
      - Kr-Ky, 2004 (Box 98, Folder 4)
      - Korea, 2004 (Box 98, Folder 5)
      - N-P, 2004 (Box 98, Folder 6)
      - Sa, 2004 (Box 98, Folder 7)
      - Scha-Scho, 2003 - 2004 (Box 98, Folder 8)
      - Schr-Schw, 1941, 2002-2004; 2002 - 2004 (Box 98, Folder 9)
      - Sci-Sey, 2004 (Box 98, Folder 10)
      - Sha-Sil, 2003 - 2005 (Box 99, Folder 1)
      - Sim-Sin, 2004 (Box 99, Folder 2)
      - Sis-Slo, 2004 (Box 99, Folder 3)
      - Sm-Sn, 2004 (Box 99, Folder 4)
      - Soa-Son, 2004 (Box 99, Folder 5)
      - Sor-Srd, 2003 - 2004 (Box 99, Folder 6)
      - Sta, 2004 (Box 99, Folder 7)
      - Stei, 2004 (Box 99, Folder 8)
      - Stel-Stev, 2004 (Box 99, Folder 9)
      - Sto-Stu, 2004 (Box 99, Folder 10)
      - Su-Sw, 2004 (Box 99, Folder 11)
      - Stevens, Ted, 2004 (Box 99, Folder 12)
      - Ta, 2004 (Box 99, Folder 13)
      - Te, 2004 (Box 100, Folder 1)
      - Th-Ti, 2004 (Box 100, Folder 2)
      - To-Tu, 2004 (Box 100, Folder 3)
      - Tv-Uk, 2003 - 2004 (Box 100, Folder 4)
      - Unc, 2004 (Box 100, Folder 5)
      - United K-N, 2004 (Box 100, Folder 6)
      - United States A-S, 2004 (Box 100, Folder 7)
      - University C-O, 2004 (Box 100, Folder 8)
      - Up-Ut, 2004 (Box 100, Folder 9)
      - Va, 2003 - 2004 (Box 100, Folder 10)
      - Ve-Vo, 2004 (Box 100, Folder 11)
      - Wa, 2003 - 2004 (Box 101, Folder 1)
      - We [includes photograph], 2003 - 2004 (Box 101, Folder 2)
      - Wh-Wl, 2004 (Box 101, Folder 3)
      - Wo, 2003 - 2004 (Box 101, Folder 4)
      - Wr-Wy, 2004 - 2005 (Box 101, Folder 5)
      - Winkler, Heinrich, 2002 - 2004 (Box 101, Folder 6)
      - X, 2004 (Box 101, Folder 7)
      - Y, 2004 (Box 101, Folder 8)
      - Za-Zd, 2004 (Box 101, Folder 9)
      - Ze-Zu, 2004 (Box 102, Folder 1)
      - Ziad, Howar, 2004 January-October (Box 102, Folder 2)
      - Ziad, Howar, 2004 November-December (Box 102, Folder 3)
      - Zogby International, 2004 January-June (Box 102, Folder 4)
      - Zogby International, 2004 July-December (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - 2005
      - Ab-Ac, 2004 - 2005 (Box 102, Folder 6)
      - Ad-Af, 2005 (Box 102, Folder 7)
      - Ag-Ak, 2005 (Box 102, Folder 8)
      - Al, 2005 (Box 102, Folder 9)
      - America, 2005 (Box 102, Folder 10)
      - American-Americas, 2005 (Box 103, Folder 1)
      - An-As, 2005 (Box 103, Folder 2)
      - At, 2005 (Box 103, Folder 3)
      - Au-Az, 2005 (Box 103, Folder 4)
      - Amazon.com, 2004 (Box 103, Folder 5)
      - Amazon.com, 2005 (Box 103, Folder 6)
      - Ba, 2005 (Box 103, Folder 7)
      - Bb-Bc, 2004 - 2005 (Box 103, Folder 8)
      - Be, 2005 (Box 103, Folder 9)
      - Bi, 2005 (Box 103, Folder 10)
      - Bl, 2005 (Box 104, Folder 1)
      - Bo-Bp, 2004 - 2005 (Box 104, Folder 2)
      - Br, 2005 (Box 104, Folder 3)
      - Bu, 2005 (Box 104, Folder 4)
      - Ca, 2005 (Box 104, Folder 5)
      - Cb-Ce, 2005 (Box 104, Folder 6)
      - Cha-Che, 2005 (Box 104, Folder 7)
      - Chi, 2005 (Box 104, Folder 8)
      - Cho-Cls, 2005 - 2007 (Box 104, Folder 9)
      - Cnb-Col, 2005 (Box 104, Folder 10)
      - Com-Cos, 2005 (Box 104, Folder 11)
      - Cou-Cze, 2004 - 2005 (Box 104, Folder 12)
      - China, 2004 - 2005 (Box 105, Folder 1)
      - Dai-Dan, 2005 (Box 105, Folder 2)
      - Dar-Del, 2005 (Box 105, Folder 3)
      - Dem-Dep, 2005 (Box 105, Folder 4)
      - Der-Dis, 2005 (Box 105, Folder 5)
      - Do-Du, 2005 (Box 105, Folder 6)
      - Dilenschneider, Robert L., 2005 January-June (Box 105, Folder 7)
      - Dilenschneider, Robert L., 2005 July-November (Box 105, Folder 8)
      - Ea-Ei, 2005 (Box 105, Folder 9)
      - El, 2005 (Box 105, Folder 10)
      - Em-Er, 2005 (Box 105, Folder 11)
      - Es-Eu, 2005 (Box 105, Folder 12)
      - Fah-Fin, 2005 (Box 106, Folder 1)
      - Fir-Fon, 2005 (Box 106, Folder 2)
      - For-Fox, 2005 (Box 106, Folder 3)
      - Fr-Fu, 2005 (Box 106, Folder 4)
      - Foreign Policy Research Institute, 2004 - 2005 (Box 106, Folder 5)
      - Ga, 2005 (Box 106, Folder 6)
      - Ge-Gi, 2004 - 2005 (Box 106, Folder 7)
      - Gl-Go, 2005 (Box 106, Folder 8)
      - Gr, 2005 (Box 106, Folder 9)
      - Gu-Gw, 2005 (Box 106, Folder 10)
      - Ha, 1946; 2004 - 2005 (Box 107, Folder 1)
      - Hb-He, 2005 (Box 107, Folder 2)
      - Hi, 2004 - 2006 (Box 107, Folder 3)
      - Hof-Hop, 2005 (Box 107, Folder 4)
      - Hor-How, 2005 (Box 107, Folder 5)
      - Hs-Hu, 2004 - 2005 (Box 107, Folder 6)
      - Hy, 2005 (Box 107, Folder 7)
      - Ib-Il, 2005 (Box 107, Folder 8)
      - Ina, 2004 - 2005 (Box 108, Folder 1)
      - Ind-Inv, 2005 (Box 108, Folder 2)
      - Ir-It, 2005 (Box 108, Folder 3)
      - India, 2005 (Box 108, Folder 4)
      - Ja, 2005 (Box 108, Folder 5)
      - Jd-Je, 2005 (Box 108, Folder 6)
      - Jo-Ju, 2005 (Box 108, Folder 7)
      - Kac-Kau, 2005 (Box 108, Folder 8)
      - Kaw-Kaz, 2005 (Box 108, Folder 9)
      - Ke, 2005 (Box 108, Folder 10)
      - Ki-Kn, 2005 (Box 108, Folder 11)
      - Ko, 2005 (Box 108, Folder 12)
      - Kr-Kw, 2005 (Box 109, Folder 1)
      - Korea, 2005 (Box 109, Folder 2)
      - Korea Society, 2005 (Box 109, Folder 3)
      - La, 2005 (Box 109, Folder 4)
      - Le, 2005 (Box 109, Folder 5)
      - Li-Ll, 2005 (Box 109, Folder 6)
      - Lo-Lu, 2005 (Box 109, Folder 7)
      - Leo Baeck Institute, 2005 (Box 109, Folder 8)
      - Ma, 2005 (Box 109, Folder 9)
      - Mc-Mh, 2004 - 2005 (Box 109, Folder 10)
      - Mi, 2005 (Box 110, Folder 1)
      - Mo, 2005 (Box 110, Folder 2)
      - Mu, 2004 - 2005 (Box 110, Folder 3)
      - Manhattan Institute, 2005 (Box 110, Folder 4)
      - Na-Nb, 2005 (Box 110, Folder 5)
      - Ne, 2005 (Box 110, Folder 6)
      - Nh-Ny, 1995 - 2005 (Box 110, Folder 7)
      - O, 2004 - 2005 (Box 110, Folder 8)
      - Pa-Pb, 2004 - 2005 (Box 110, Folder 9)
      - Pe, 2005 (Box 110, Folder 10)
      - Pf-Pl, 2005 (Box 111, Folder 1)
      - Po, 2004 - 2006 (Box 111, Folder 2)
      - Pr-Py, 2005 (Box 111, Folder 3)
      - Pelican Publishing Company, 2005 - 2006 (Box 111, Folder 4)
      - Q, 2005 (Box 111, Folder 5)
      - Ra-Rh, 2005 (Box 111, Folder 6)
      - Ri, 2004 - 2005 (Box 111, Folder 7)
      - Roa-Roo, 2004 - 2005 (Box 111, Folder 8)
      - Rop-Roy, 2005 (Box 111, Folder 9)
      - Ru-Ry, 2003 - 2005 (Box 111, Folder 10)
      - Rostow, Nicholas, 2005 (Box 111, Folder 11)
      - Sab-Sar, 2005 (Box 112, Folder 1)
      - Sau-Saw, 2005 (Box 112, Folder 2)
      - Scha-Schn, 2005 (Box 112, Folder 3)
      - Scho-Scow, 2004 - 2005 (Box 112, Folder 4)
      - Se, 2004 - 2005 (Box 112, Folder 5)
      - Sh, 2004 - 2005 (Box 112, Folder 6)
      - Si, 2005 (Box 112, Folder 7)
      - Sk-Sn, 2005 (Box 112, Folder 8)
      - So, 1986, 2005; 2005 (Box 112, Folder 9)
      - Sp, 2005 (Box 113, Folder 1)
      - St, 2004 - 2005 (Box 113, Folder 2)
      - Su-Sy, 1961, 2005; 2005 (Box 113, Folder 3)
      - Schurtenberger, Erwin, 2005 (Box 113, Folder 4)
      - Ta-Te, 2005 (Box 113, Folder 5)
      - Th, 2005 (Box 113, Folder 6)
      - Ti-Tr, 2005 (Box 113, Folder 7)
      - Tu-Tw, 2005 (Box 113, Folder 8)
      - Uj-Uk, 2005 (Box 113, Folder 9)
      - Un-Us, 2004 - 2005 (Box 113, Folder 10)
      - Va-Ve, 2005 (Box 114, Folder 1)
      - Vi-Vu, 2005 (Box 114, Folder 2)
      - Wag-Wat, 2005 (Box 114, Folder 3)
      - Wee-Wei, 2005 (Box 114, Folder 4)
      - Wel-Wey, 2005 (Box 114, Folder 5)
      - Wh-Wj, 2002 - 2005 (Box 114, Folder 6)
      - Wo-Wr, 2005 (Box 114, Folder 7)
      - Wu-Wy, 2004 - 2005 (Box 114, Folder 8)
      - Weigel, George, 2004 - 2005 (Box 114, Folder 9)
      - White House, 2005 January-March (Box 114, Folder 10)
      - White House, 2005 April-July (Box 115, Folder 1)
      - White House, 2005 August-November (Box 115, Folder 2)
      - X, 2005 (Box 115, Folder 3)
      - Y, 2005 (Box 115, Folder 4)
      - Za-Zd, 2004 - 2005 (Box 115, Folder 5)
      - Ze-Zi, 2005 (Box 115, Folder 6)
      - Zo-Zu, 2005 (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - 2006
      - Ab-Ad, 2005 - 2006 (Box 115, Folder 8)
      - Ae-Aj, 2006 (Box 115, Folder 9)
      - Ak, 2006 (Box 115, Folder 10)
      - Alb-Alj, 2005 - 2006 (Box 115, Folder 11)
      - All, 2006 (Box 116, Folder 1)
      - Am, 2004 - 2006 (Box 116, Folder 2)
      - An-Ar [includes photograph], 2006 (Box 116, Folder 3)
      - As, 2006 (Box 116, Folder 4)
      - At, 2006 (Box 116, Folder 5)
      - Au-Az, 2005 - 2006 (Box 116, Folder 6)
      - Ailes, Roger, 2006 (Box 116, Folder 7)
      - Ba, 2006 (Box 116, Folder 8)
      - Bb-Bc, 2006 (Box 116, Folder 9)
      - Be-Bh, 2006 (Box 116, Folder 10)
      - Bi, 2005 - 2006 (Box 116, Folder 11)
      - Bla-Blo, 2006 (Box 116, Folder 12)
      - Blu-Boy, 2006 (Box 117, Folder 1)
      - Bra-Bri, 2005 - 2006 (Box 117, Folder 2)